Guide to the Max S. Baucus Papers 1958-2016 (bulk 1974-2014)
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula
- Photographs, 1958-2014; Series XIII; 29.6 linear feet; 281.9 gigabytes
  - Photographs, 1959-2013; Sub-series 1; 25.7 linear feet
    - 1998 0610 MSB with Korea President Kim Dae-Jung, June 10, 1998; Max Baucus at working coffee meeting in honor of President Kim Dae-Jung of South Korea. (Box-folder Series 13 - 41/2)
    - 1998 0610 WH Trans Equity Act Bill Signing, June 10, 1998; Max Baucus at HR 2400 Transportation Equity Act signing with President Bill Clinton and constituents. (Box-folder Series 13 - 41/3)
    - 1998 0614 DC NBC Meet the Press, June 14, 1998; Max Baucus speaking on NBC Meet the Press. (Box-folder Series 13 - 41/4)
    - 1998 0616 DC John Glenn Dinner, June 16, 1998; Max Baucus at reception and dinner honoring John Glenn at the Air and Space Museum with constituents. Signed, with letter.. (Box-folder Series 13 - 41/5)
    - 1998 0624-0703 F China Trip, June 24-July 3, 1998; Max Baucus on China trip with President Bill Clinton and constituents. (Box-folder Series 13 - 41/6-10)
    - 1998 0626 Congressional Delegation, June 26, 1998; Max Baucus with Congressional delegation, likely on China trip. (Box-folder Series 13 - 41/11)
    - 1998 0704 MT Great Falls Fourth of July, July 4, 1998; Max Baucus at Fourth of July parade in Great Falls, Montana with clowns. (Box-folder Series 13 - 41/12)
    - 1998 0723 DC Nelson Mandela, July 23, 1998; Max Baucus shaking hands with Nelson Mandela. (Box-folder Series 13 - 41/13)
    - 1998 0815-0821 F South American Trade Mission Brazil, August 15-21, 1998; Max Baucus on South American trade trip to Brazil with constituents. (Box-folder Series 13 - 41/14)
    - 1998 0824 MT Great Falls Social Security Forum, 1998 0826 MT Havre Social Security Forum, August 24-26, 1998; Max Baucus at Social Security forums in Great Falls, Montana and Havre, Montana with constituents and Mack McConnell, Ray Young, Greg Kecskes, Charlotte Thomas, Beverly Robinson, Raynita Meyer, Arlene (last name unknown) and Pat Stingel, Jack Gunderson, George McGovern, Kathleen Murray, Martin Jakubowski, Clyde Springer, Joe Heavey. (Box-folder Series 13 - 41/15)
    - 1998 0825 MT Billings Shiloh Interchange, August 25, 1998; Max Baucus at Shiloh Interchange in Billings, Montana holding shovels with Transportation Commission Chairman Thorm Forseth; Yellowstone County Commission Chairman Bill Kennedy; Director of Transportation Marvin Dye; Senator Conrad Burns; representative for Congressman Hill, Tom Nelson; assistant division administrator of FHWA Jerry Cloud; Billings Mayor Charles Tooley. (Box-folder Series 13 - 41/16)
    - 1998 0826 MT Havre Social Security Forum, August 26, 1998; Max Baucus at Social Security forum in Havre, Montana with Arlene(last name unknown) and Pat Stingel; Clyde Springer; Joe Heavey. (Box-folder Series 13 - 41/17)
    - 1998 0827 MT Browning MDOT and SK Construction Workday, August 27, 1998; Max Baucus at Browning MDOT and SK Construction workday with constituents. (Box-folder Series 13 - 41/18-19)
    - 1998 0925 DC NASA Astronauts, September 25, 1998; Max Baucus with NASA astronauts Terry W., Joe Elwab, Jim R.. (Box-folder Series 13 - 41/20)
    - 1998 1029 FL Kennedy Space Center Cape Canaveral John Glenn Shuttle Launch NASA, October 29, 1998; Max Baucus at Kennedy Space Center Cape Canaveral in Florida at NASA John Glenn shuttle launch for Discovery. (Box-folder Series 13 - 41/21-22)
    - 1998 10 and 11 White House with Al Gore, October-November 1998; Max Baucus at Malaysian embassy welcome and at White House, with Vice President Al Gore. (Box-folder Series 13 - 41/23)
    - 1998 1101 MT Butte Campaign Door to Door, November 1, 1998; Max Baucus campaigning door-to-door in Butte, Montana with constituents. (Box-folder Series 13 - 41/24)
    - 1998 1101 MT Butte Campaign Door to Door, 1998 1101 MT Butte Campaign Probably Democratic Dinner at Copper King, 1998 1102 T Bozeman Rural Development Annual Meeting, 1998 1102 MT Campaign Yellowstone County Democratic Rally, 1998 1103 MT Wisdom Jackson School Workday, 1999 0215 MT Kalispell Sorenson Clinic Workday, November 1, 1998-February 15, 1999; Max Baucus campaigning door-to-door in Butte, Montana with constituents, at likely Democratic dinner at Copper King in Butte with constituents, at Bozeman Rural Development annual meeting, at Yellowstone County Democratic party, at Jackson School workday in Wisdom, Montana in classroom with students. (Box-folder Series 13 - 41/25)
    - 1998 1101 MT Butte Campaign Probably Democratic Dinner at Copper King, November 1, 1998; Max Baucus at likely Democratic dinner at Copper King in Butte, Montana with constituents. (Box-folder Series 13 - 41/26)
    - 1998 1102 MT Bozeman Rural Development Annual Meeting, November 2, 1998; Max Baucus at Bozeman Rural Development annual meeting with constituents. (Box-folder Series 13 - 41/27)
    - 1998 1102 MT Campaign Yellowstone County Democratic party, November 2, 1998; Max Baucus at Yellowstone County Democratic party with constituents. (Box-folder Series 13 - 41/28)
    - 1998 1103 MT Wisdom Jackson School Workday, November 3, 1998; Max Baucus at Jackson School workday in Wisdom, Montana in classroom with students. (Box-folder Series 13 - 41/29)
    - 1998 1108 MSB with Bill Clinton at Camp David, November 8, 1998; Max Baucus at Camp David with President Bill Clinton and constituent. (Box-folder Series 13 - 41/30)
    - 1998 1118-1123 F Japan, Korea, and Guam Trip with President Clinton and Hillary Clinton, November 18-23, 1998; Max Baucus on Japan, Korea, and Guam trip with President Bill Clinton; First Lady Hillary Rodham Clinton; Representative Robert Underwood of Guam; Representative Earl Pomeroy of North Dakota; Representative Neil Abercrombie of Hawaii; constituents, and Max Baucus speaking to Japanese students at the Tokyo American Center of the American Embassy. (Box-folder Series 13 - 41/31)
    - 1998 1118-1123 F Japan, Korea, and Guam Trip with President Clinton and Hillary Clinton, November 18-23, 1998; Max Baucus on Japan, Korea, and Guam trip with President Bill Clinton; First Lady Hillary Rodham Clinton; Representative Robert Underwood of Guam; Representative Earl Pomeroy of North Dakota; Representative Neil Abercrombie of Hawaii; constituents, and Max Baucus speaking to Japanese students at the Tokyo American Center of the American Embassy. (Box-folder Series 13 - 42/1)
    - 1998 1202 Meeting at WH with Bill Clinton and Dem Caucus, December 2, 1998; Max Baucus at White House with President Bill Clinton and members of the Democratic Caucus. (Box-folder Series 13 - 42/2)
    - 1998 1206 MT Bird Hunting, December 6, 1998; Max Baucus bird hunting at Overstreet Ranch with constituents. (Box-folder Series 13 - 42/3-7)
    - 1998 DC All Staff Posed Outdoors, Max Baucus with staff posed on Capitol steps, Nancy Hadley, intern Jennifer Sallem, intern Leah Nichols, Shandra Wilcox, intern Andrew Nelson, Scott Olsen, intern Cliff Jones, intern Justin Ranney, Brian Kuehl, Ed Cox, Julie Wirkkala, Giano Cromley, Angela Marshal, intern John Shepard, Pat Bousilman, Zak Anderson, Mark Jette, Maria Freese, Chris Niedermeier, Molly Molloy, Maureen Rice, Torian Donohoe, Marcie Evans, intern Erin Casey, intern Matt McKenna, Bill Lombardi, Sara Johnson, intern Jim Frisk, Brian Cavey, Jessie Pannoni, Rhonda Simard. (Box-folder Series 13 - 42/8)
    - 1998 MT Billings Sacrifice Cliff Visit with Others Including Bill Kennedy, Max Baucus visiting Sacrifice Cliff near Billings, Montana with Bill Kennedy and constituents. (Box-folder Series 13 - 42/9)
    - 1998 MT Maybe Town Hall Meeting Eastern MT, Max Baucus at likely town hall meeting in eastern Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 42/10)
    - 1998 MT Speaking with Constituents Indoors and Outdoors Eastern MT, Max Baucus speaking with constituents in eastern Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 42/11)
    - 1998 MT Standing Outdoors with Group Building in Background Eastern MT, Max Baucus outdoors with constituents in eastern Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 42/12)
    - 1998 MT Standing and Seated with Constituents Two Events, Max Baucus standing and seated with constituents at two events. (Box-folder Series 13 - 42/13)
    - 1998 MT Talking with Constituents Indoors Maybe Senior Citizens Center Eastern MT, Max Baucus with constituents, at possibly senior citizens center in eastern Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 42/14)
    - 1998 MT Unknown Elementary School Students, Max Baucus with elementary school students in classroom. (Box-folder Series 13 - 42/15)
    - 1998 MT Standing Outdoors with Group Building in Background Eastern MT, 1998 MT Speaking with Constituents Indoors and Outdoors Eastern MT, 1998 MT Maybe Town Hall Meeting Eastern MT, 1998 MT Talking with Constituents Indoors Maybe Senior Citizens Center Eastern MT, Max Baucus at likely town hall meeting in eastern Montana, speaking with constituents in eastern Montana, outdoors with constituents in eastern Montana, with constituents, at possibly senior citizens center in eastern Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 42/16)
    - 1999 0105 EPW 105th Congress, January 5, 1999; Max Baucus with Environment and Public Works EPW Senate Committee of the 105th Congress. (Box-folder Series 13 - 42/17)
    - 1999 01 MT Maybe Roundtable or Meeting, January 1999; Max Baucus at roundtable or meeting with constituents. (Box-folder Series 13 - 42/18)
    - 1999 0215 MT Kalispell Sorensen Clinic Workday, February 15, 1999; Max Baucus at Sorensen Clinic workday in Kalispell, Montana with constituents. (Box-folder Series 13 - 42/19)
    - 1999 0218 MT Helena Jefferson School Kindergarten Escort to MT Legislature Speech, February 18, 1999; Max Baucus escorting Jefferson School kindergarten class to Montana Legislature speech in Helena, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 42/20)
    - 1999 0330 MT Kalispell Economic Development Plan Announcement at Outlaw Inn, March 30, 1999; Max Baucus announcing economic development plan at the Outlaw Inn in Kalispell, Montana with constituents. (Box-folder Series 13 - 42/21)
    - 1999 0330 MT Kalispell Economic Development Plan Announcement at Outlaw Inn, and others, March 30-April 1, 1999; Max Baucus announcing economic development plan at the Outlaw Inn in Kalispell, Montana with constituents; visiting Bigfork Art and Cultural Center being presented with hat and t-shirt by constituent; at Bigfork High School visit with student; at senior citizens lunch in Bigfork, Montana; at Kalispell UPS visit; at Democratic campaign reception at Knead Cafe in Kalispell; with FVCC student leadership program in Kalispell. Includes negatives.. (Box-folder Series 13 - 42/22)
    - 1999 0331 MT Bigfork High School Visit, March 31, 1999; Max Baucus at Bigfork High School visit with student. (Box-folder Series 13 - 42/23)
    - 1999 0331 MT Bigfork Lunch with Senior Citizens, March 31, 1999; Max Baucus at senior citizens lunch in Bigfork, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 42/24)
    - 1999 0331 MT Bigfork Art and Cultural Center Visit, March 31, 1999; Max Baucus visiting Bigfork Art and Cultural Center being presented with hat and t-shirt by constituent. (Box-folder Series 13 - 42/25)
    - 1999 0331 MT Kalispell Visit UPS, March 31, 1999; Max Baucus at Kalispell, Montana UPS visit. (Box-folder Series 13 - 42/26)
    - 1999 0331 MT Kalispell Dinner with Labor Union, March 31, 1999; Max Baucus at labor union dinner in Kalispell, Montana with constituents. (Box-folder Series 13 - 42/27)
    - 1999 03 MT Bowling with Former Staff, March 1999; Max Baucus bowling with staff. (Box-folder Series 13 - 42/28)
    - 1999 03 MT Bowling with Former Staff, 1999 0401 MT Kalispell Work with Up with People Volunteers, 1999 0331 MT Kalispell Dinner with Labor Union, March-April 1999; Max Baucus bowling with staff,. (Box-folder Series 13 - 42/29)
    - 1999 0401 MT Kalispell Work with Up with People Volunteers, April 1, 1999; Max Baucus working with Up with People volunteers in Kalispell, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 42/30)
    - 1999 0401 MT Kalispell Campaign Democratic Reception at Knead Café, April 1, 1999; Max Baucus at Democratic campaign reception at the Knead Café in Kalispell, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 42/31)
    - 1999 0401 MT Kalispell FVCC Student Program RE Leadership, April 1, 1999; Max Baucus with FVCC student leadership program in Kalispell, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 42/32)
    - 1999 0423 MT Missoula Chinese Delegation Including Ambassador Li Zhaoxing, 1999 0602 MT Plentywood Town Hall Meeting, 1999 0602 MT Scobey Meet and Vision Net with Constituents, 1999 0603 MT Culbertson Tour Montola Plant, 1999 0603 MT Poplar Chief Medicine Bear Complex Groundbreaking, April 23-June 3, 1999; Max Baucus with Chinese delegation, including Ambassador Li Zhaoxing, in Missoula, Montana; at town hall meeting in Plentywood, Montana; at meet at Vision Net with constituents in Scobey, Montana; touring Motorola plant in Culbertson, Montana; at Chief Medicine Bear Complex groundbreaking in Poplar, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 42/33)
    - 1999 0408 MSB with Bill Clinton at WH Dinner for Chinese Premier, April 8, 1999; Max Baucus with at White House dinner for Chinese Premier Zhu Rongji and Madame Leo An with President Bill Clinton. (Box-folder Series 13 - 42/34)
    - 1999 0411-0412 F Macedonia Albania Senate Appropriations Committee, April 11-12, 1999; Max Baucus on Macedonia and Albania trip for the Senate Appropriations Codel Leadership visit. (Box-folder Series 13 - 42/35)
    - 1999 0423 MT Missoula Chinese Delegation Including Ambassador Li Zhaoxing, April 23, 1999; Max Baucus with Chinese delegation, including Ambassador Li Zhaoxing, in Missoula, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 42/36)
    - 1999 0522 MT Coal Banks Landing Canoe Trip with Babbitt and Ambrose, May 22, 1999; Max Baucus at Coal Banks Landing canoe trip with Babbitt and Ambrose. (Box-folder Series 13 - 42/37)
    - 1999 0527 Speaking at Podium, May 27, 1999; Max Baucus speaking at podium at event. (Box-folder Series 13 - 42/38)
    - 1999 05 MSB with Japanese Prime Minister Obuchi, May 1999; Max Baucus with Japanese Prime Minister Obuchi. (Box-folder Series 13 - 42/39)
    - 1999 0602 MT Plentywood Town Hall Meeting, June 2, 1999; Max Baucus at town hall meeting in Plentywood, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 42/40)
    - 1999 0602 MT Scobey Meet and Vision Net with Constituents, June 2, 1999; Max Baucus at meet at Vision Net with constituents in Scobey, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 43/1)
    - 1999 0603 MT Culbertson Tour Motorola Plant, June 3, 1999; Max Baucus touring Motorola plant in Culbertson, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 43/2-3)
    - 1999 0603 MT Poplar Chief Medicine Bear Complex Groundbreaking, June 3, 1999; Max Baucus at Chief Medicine Bear Complex groundbreaking in Poplar, TM. (Box-folder Series 13 - 43/4-5)
    - 1999 0604 MT Sidney Health Center Workday, June 4, 1999; Max Baucus at Sidney Health Center workday with constituents. (Box-folder Series 13 - 43/6)
    - 1999 0621 MT Great Falls Reading to Children with Secretary Riley, June 21, 1999; Max Baucus reading to children in Great Falls, Montana with Secretary of Education Richard Riley. (Box-folder Series 13 - 43/7)
    - 1999 0621 MT Bozeman and Great Falls Education Secretary Richard Riley Visit, June 21, 1999; Max Baucus in Bozeman and Great Falls, Montana with Secretary of Education Richard Riley. (Box-folder Series 13 - 43/8)
    - 1999 0621 MT Bozeman and Great Falls Education Secretary Richard Riley Visit, 1999 0621 MT Great Falls Reading to Children with Secretary Riley, June 21, 1999; Max Baucus reading to children in Great Falls, Montana with Secretary of Education Richard Riley and in Bozeman and Great Falls with Secretary of Education Richard Riley. (Box-folder Series 13 - 43/9)
    - 1999 0720 DC Washington International Trade Association RE Service Award, July 20, 1999; Max Baucus speech introduction by Peter at Washington International Trade Association event at Mayflower Hotel in D.C. for service award. (Box-folder Series 13 - 43/10)
    - 1999 0721 MSB with Bill Clinton at WH Medicare Announcement, July 21, 1999; Max Baucus shaking hands with President Bill Clinton at the White House for Medicare announcement. (Box-folder Series 13 - 43/11)
    - 1999 0803 MSB with Al Gore at Senate Ag Meeting, August 3, 1999; Max Baucus with Vice President Al Gore and constituents at Senate agriculture meeting. (Box-folder Series 13 - 43/12)
    - 1999 0807 MT Bozeman Sweet Pea Run Parade, August 7, 1999; Max Baucus at Sweet Pea Run parade in Bozeman, Montana riding horse. (Box-folder Series 13 - 43/13)
    - 1999 0809 MT Belgrade Interchange Ceremony at Clarkin Park, August 9, 1999; Max Baucus at Belgrade Interchange ceremony at Clarkin Park with constituents. (Box-folder Series 13 - 43/14)
    - 1999 0809 MT Belgrade Steak Fry with USDA Staff, August 9, 1999; Max Baucus at steak fry in Belgrade, Montana with USDA staff. (Box-folder Series 13 - 43/15)
    - 1999 0809 MT Bozeman Breakfast with Bozeman Area Women, August 9, 1999; Max Baucus at breakfast with women in Bozeman, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 43/16)
    - 1999 0809 MT Bozeman Tour Pathways Personal Care and Timberline, August 9, 1999; Max Baucus on Bozeman, Montana tour at Pathways Personal Care and Timberline. (Box-folder Series 13 - 43/17-18)
    - 1999 0809 MT Bozeman Tour Valley Ice Gardens, August 9, 1999; Max Baucus on Bozeman, Montana tour at Valley Ice Gardens. (Box-folder Series 13 - 43/19-20)
    - 1999 0810 MT Bozeman Medicare Forum at Deaconess Hospital, August 10, 1999; Max Baucus at Medicare forum at Deaconess Hospital in Bozeman, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 43/21)
    - 1999 08 MT MSB in Montana Shirt with Mike Overstreet and Other Man, August 1999; Max Baucus wearing Montana shirt with Mike Overstreet and constituent. (Box-folder Series 13 - 43/22)
    - 1999 0903 MT Missoula, Billings, Butte Watkins Shephard Trucking, September 3, 1999; Max Baucus at Watkins Shephard Trucking in Missoula, Billings, and Butte, Montana with constituents. (Box-folder Series 13 - 43/23-25)
    - 1999 0903 MT Missoula, Billings, Butte Watkins Shephard Trucking, September 3, 1999; Max Baucus at Watkins Shephard Trucking in Missoula, Billings, and Butte, Montana with constituents. (Box-folder Series 13 - 44/1-2)
    - 1999 0916 DC MSB with Jake and Janet Cummins of Bozeman, September 16, 1999; Max Baucus with constituents Jake and Janet Cummins of Bozeman, Montana in the Montana Conference Room in D.C.. (Box-folder Series 13 - 44/3)
    - 1999 0918 MT Missoula Village Health Care, September 18, 1999; Max Baucus at Village Health Care in Missoula, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 44/4)
    - 1999 0919 MT Great Falls Rankin Run, September 19, 1999; Max Baucus at Rankin Run in Great Falls, Montana with Madeline Bidwell, Paul Comen, and constituents. (Box-folder Series 13 - 44/5)
    - 1999 0920 MT Helena 3RS Preschool Reading, September 20, 1999; Max Baucus at 3RS Preschool reading in Helena, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 44/6)
    - 1999 0921 DC Treasury Secretary Larry Summers Dinner, September 21, 1999; Max Baucus at dinner hosted by Secretary of the Treasury Larry Summers in the Cash Room at the Treasury with constituents and. (Box-folder Series 13 - 44/7)
    - 1999 1001 MSB with Bill Clinton, Harry Reid, and Bryan, October 1, 1999; Max Baucus with President Bill Clinton, Senator Harry Reid, and Bryan (last name unknown) likely on airplane. (Box-folder Series 13 - 44/8)
    - 1999 1009 MT Missoula UM Homecoming Parade, October 9, 1999; Max Baucus at University of Montana UM homecoming parade in Missoula, Montana with constituents. (Box-folder Series 13 - 44/9)
    - 1999 MT Missoula UM Grizzlies Homecoming, October 9, 1999; Max Baucus at University of Montana UM Grizzlies homecoming and at homecoming Bloody Mary Party with constituents Maureen Ford, Sharon Lenard, Dick Ford, Bob Crippen. (Box-folder Series 13 - 44/10)
    - 1999 1011 MT Jefferson City Alta Mine Visit, October 11, 1999; Max Baucus at Alta Mine visit in Jefferson City with constituents. (Box-folder Series 13 - 44/11)
    - 1999 1025 MSB with Bill Clinton at Prescription Drug Event, October 25, 1999; Max Baucus with President Bill Clinton and constituents at prescription drug event. (Box-folder Series 13 - 44/12)
    - 1999 1211-1215 F China, December 11-15, 1999; Max Baucus on Beijing, China trip with Ira Wolf; Lorenzo Goco; Colonel Tim Peterson; executive Vice President of ARATS, Tang Shubei; President of CPIFA Mei Zhaorong; DCS of PLA General Xiong Guangkai; Vice President of CPAFFC, Li Xiaolin; Gene Martin of DCM; Li Shanlin of Li Family Restaurant; Premier Rhu Zongji of China; Agriculture Minister Chen Yaobang. (Box-folder Series 13 - 44/13)
    - 2000 0217 MT Hamilton Bitterroot Drug Workday, February 17, 2000; Max Baucus at Bitterroot Drug workday in Hamilton, Montana with constituents. (Box-folder Series 13 - 44/14)
    - 2000 0223 MT Great Falls Ag and Eco Development Event with a Chinese Delegation, February 23, 2000; Max Baucus at agriculture and eco development event in Great Falls, Montana with a Chinese delegation. (Box-folder Series 13 - 44/15)
    - 2000 0329 MSB with Egyptian President Hosni Mubarak, March 29, 2000; Max Baucus shaking hands with Egyptian President Hosni Mubarak. (Box-folder Series 13 - 44/16)
    - 2000 0510 DC Florida Council of 100, May 10, 2000; Max Baucus speaking about trade and the World Trade Organization WTO, to Florida Council of 100 in Washington, D.C. (Box-folder Series 13 - 44/17)
    - 2000 0512 MT Missoula Mansfield Statue Dedication, May 12, 2000; Max Baucus at Mansfield statue dedication at the University of Montana UM in Missoula, Montana with constituents. (Box-folder Series 13 - 44A/1)
    - 2000 0523 White House Moynihan Courthouse Naming Signing, May 23, 2000; Max Baucus at Moynihan Courthouse naming signing at the White House. (Box-folder Series 13 - 44A/2)
    - 2000 0608 DC Press Conference RE Brownfields, 2000 DC Former Staff, June 8, 2000; Max Baucus at Brownfields press conference with constituents, and with former staff in Washington, D.C. (Box-folder Series 13 - 44A/3)
    - 2000 0613 DC WH Medicare Prescription Press Conference, June 13, 2000; Max Baucus speaking at Medicare prescriptions press conference with President Bill Clinton and constituents, and at POTUS Rural Report OEOB. (Box-folder Series 13 - 44A/4)
    - 2000 0619 MSB Skeet Shooting, June 19, 2000; Max Baucus skeet shooting. (Box-folder Series 13 - 44A/5)
    - 2000 0621 DC Bill Clinton China Permanent Trade Relations, June 21, 2000; Max Baucus at China permanent trade relations event shaking hands with President Bill Clinton. (Box-folder Series 13 - 45/1)
    - 2000 0625-0626 MT Great Falls Economic Summit, June 25-26, 2000; Max Baucus at economic summit in Great Falls, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 45/2-3)
    - 2000 0625-0626 MT Great Falls Economic Summit, 2000 D.C. MSB in Office, 2000 DC WH Unknown Press Conference, June 25-26, 2000; Max Baucus economic summit in Great Falls, Montana; in D.C. office; at press conference at the White House. (Box-folder Series 13 - 45/4)
    - 2000 0625-0626 MT Great Falls Economic Summit, 2000 MT Scenery No MSB, June 25-26, 2000; Max Baucus at economic summit in Great Falls, Montana and Montana scenery, no Baucus. (Box-folder Series 13 - 45/5)
    - 2000 07 MT Kalispell Office, July 2000; Baucus staff in front of Kalispell, Montana office, no Baucus. (Box-folder Series 13 - 45/6)
    - 2000 0812 MT Helena Fires and James Lee Witt and Burns, August 12, 2000; Max Baucus discussing Helena, Montana fires with James Lee Witt and Burns, Ron Mercer and Jim C.. (Box-folder Series 13 - 45/7)